William Dixon

Denver, CO

Full Stack Developer (719)321-3014

Wdixon2186@gmail.com https://www.linkedin.com/in/williammdixon/

SKILLS:

Final Cut Pro X, HTML, CSS, Javascript, React Node.js, Express, Bootstrap, Python, Django

PROJECTS:

Trivia: Designed trivia game using HTML, CSS, and Javascript based on famous quotes from wide released movies.

https://wdixon2186.github.io/movieTrivia/

Local Library: worked successfully with NODE.js, Express, Mongoose, HBS, and CSS to build a fully functioning database that housed information on books and movies I own.

https://books-and-movies-db.herokuapp.com/movies

City Fyndr: Worked in a team using Node.js, Express, React.js, Boot-strap, and CSS to develop an app that allows users to find census data on the top 50 cities in the United States.

https://wdixon2186.github.io/City-Search-Front-End/#/

Internet Makes A Movie: Built using Django, Python, and HTML, the site serves as a social media platform for people to submit screenplay pages that build off of other users projects. https://internet-makes-a-movie.herokuapp.com/

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Caption Call, Colorado Springs, CO

August 2018 – August 2019

Communications Assistant

• Transcribed phone calls for those who are hard of hearing by accessing dragon software, and repeating the conversation.

Torch Middle School, City of Industry, CA

January 2018 – June 2018

Film and Video Volunteer Instructor

- Developed and gave lessons on the analytics of different films, and the meanings that can be drawn from different techniques.
- Walked students through the editing software of final cut pro.

PATHFINDER MEDIA, Los Angeles, CA

August 2017 - December

2017

Development Intern

- Managed and evaluated over forty screenplays, including the writing of script coverage.
- Researched and noted potential clients by their previous work and recent successes.

EDUCATION:

Software Engineering Certificate, General Assembly Bachelor of Arts Film Studies, Azusa Pacific University